(Transcribed by TurboScribe. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) Barb was celebrating her birthday today.
She was turning seven years old.
All her friends were coming.
Her relatives were also coming.
She was going to see her cousins, uncles,
and aunts.
Even her neighbor was coming.
Her parents got her a cake with a
horse on it.
Horses were her favorite animal.
Her dad spent all day decorating their house.
There were balloons, banners, and streamers.
She was so happy when she saw the
decorations and everyone.
This was her best birthday ever.
She had a jumper for her and her
friends to play with.
She also had party gifts.
Barb got a lot of presents.
She thanked everyone for coming.
She hugged her parents.